keralahousedesigns.com 2019-06-20

# Privacy Policy - Kerala home design and floor plans

**Privacy Policy for www.keralahousedesigns.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at keralahomedesign@gmail.com.

At www.keralahousedesigns.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.keralahousedesigns.com and how it is used.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.keralahousedesigns.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. Visitors to this website who have javascript enabled are tracked using Google Analytics. This data is primarily used to optimize our website for our visitors, however we will use this data for marketing purposes. An example of how this data could be used for marketing purposes would be to tell potential advertisers how many visitors we get to the website, where our visitors come from, and how they arrive at our website. This data DOES NOT include any personalized identification information.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.keralahousedesigns.com.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.keralahousedesigns.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....

Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.keralahousedesigns.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.keralahousedesigns.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.keralahousedesigns.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

## Popular Posts - All Time

An orthographic view of some vertical feature of a house. (Front, rear, side, interior elevation)in other words exterior face of a building ...

Ground Floor Plan - 1155.51 Sq. Feet Total Built Uo Area - 1155.51 Sq. Feet Designer:Shiju Kottathazha EIDC Muscat / Calicut Click on e...

These Beautiful Home interior designs got as email. So don't know the sources. 

Some Western Style House Exterior Design
